Like you just saw, the main problem with tracking multiple metrics
就像你刚刚说到的 追踪多个指标的主要问题是假正例
is that a false positive, which should be a rare event,
原本罕见的事情会变得更常见
becomes more common as you increase the number of metrics you're measuring.
随着你增加测试的指标数量
As you might guess, the main way to fix this is to use a higher
你可能会思忖 解决这个问题的主要方式
confidence level for each individual metric
是使用置信度高的单个指标
in order to bring down the overall probability of a false positive.
从而降低出现假正例的总概率
Exactly what confidence level you use depends on how conservative
具体使用什么样的置信度
you want to be.
取决于你想要多保守的结果
The first method you might think of is to assume that
你可能会想到的第一种方式是
the metrics are independent of each other.
假设每个指标是相互独立的
Then you can use the same equation that I used earlier to calculate
然后你可以使用
the overall alpha.
我之前计算总 α 时使用的相同的等式
But instead,
但是
this time you would set the overall alpha to be what you wanted, maybe .05.
这次你要把总的 α 设置为你想要的 如 0.05
And then solve for the individual alpha you needed in order to get the overall
然后解决你需要的单个 α
alpha you're happy with.
得出你想要的总 α
However, there's a different method that people are more likely to use in
然而 还有不同的方法
practice called the Bonferroni correction.
人们更有可能在实践中使用 Bonferroni 校正法
The Bonferroni correction has two main advantages.
Bonferroni 校正法有两大优势
It's very simple to calculate and it doesn't make any assumptions.
方便计算 没有任何假设
That is, it doesn't assume independence like our method one did.
就是说 它不像我们使用的方法一样假设独立性
The Bonferroni method is also very conservative.
Bonferroni 的方法也很保守
It's guaranteed to give an alpha overall at least as small as you specified.
它保证给出总的 α 值至少像你确定的那样小
And again, it does this without making any assumptions.
记住 它不做任何假设
Depending on your use case, this might or might not be what you want.
取决于你的使用情况 可能是也可能不是你想要的
To use the Bonferroni correction, you calculate the individual
使用 Bonferroni 校正计算你要使用每个指标的 α 值
alpha you should use for each metric by taking the overall alpha you want and
利用你想要的总 α 值
dividing by the number of metrics.
除以指标数量
So if you have N equals three metrics, and you want your overall probability of
那么 如果 N 表示有 3 个指标
a false positive to be 0.05 or less than the individual
你想要假正例的总概率为 0.05 或者小于
alpha that you would use for the significance test of each metrics.
你要在每个指标的重要测试中使用的单个 α 值
Would be 0.05 divided by 3 or 0.0167.
那会是 0.05 除以 3 等于 0.0167
If you want to see a proof of why this method works,
如果你想要确定为什么这个方法会奏效
see the instructor's notes.
查看讲师注释
The main problem with the Bonferroni correction is that often, you'll
Bonferroni 校正的主要问题是
be tracking metrics that are correlated and all tend to move at the same time.
你要追踪彼此相互联系 可能同时移动的指标
In which case, this method is too conservative.
在那种情况下 这个方法太过保守
In our coaching example from earlier.
在我们之前参与辅导的例子中
If users are adopting coaching earlier in the course,
如果用户在课程早期选择参与辅导
it's likely that the probability of adoption is also going up and
选择的概率会一直上升
the price is probably more likely to change also.
价格也越有可能发生变化
So, in this case, the Bonferroni method is probably too conservative for
所以 在这个例子中 Bonferroni 校正法
Audacity's need.
对 Audacity 来说可能太保守了
That will lead to them launching fewer experiments than they would like.
这会导致它们发布比他们预期更少的实验
Now, suppose Audacity runs an experiment where they update one of
现在 假设 Audacity 进行一个实验
the descriptions on the course list.
更新课程表中的一个描述
We talked about some metrics that might be good for
我们在第三课中谈到一些指标
this experiment in lesson three.
可能对这个实验有用
They almost certainly want to track the probability of clicking
它们想要追踪
through to the course overview page from the course list.
从课程表点击访问课程概览页面的概率
But it's also a good idea to track continued progression down the funnel
但也是个好主意 继续追踪后续进展
to catch whether the updated description is misleading.
得知更新了的描述是否具有误导性
So suppose,
那么假设
Audacity also measures the average time spent reading the course overview page.
Audacity 也测试浏览课程概览页面的平均时间
The probability of enrolling in the course, given that you reached
注册这个课程的概率 假设你进入
the course overview page, and the average time spent in the classroom for
这个课程的概览页面
this course during the first week after enrollment.
在注册后的第一周 在这个教室 花在这个课程上的平均时间
Now, here is the measured difference as well as the standard error for
这是每个指标测试出的差异
each metric.
和标准误差
You can assume that each metric is normally distributed.
你可以假设每个指标是标准发布的
Now, which of these metrics showed a statistically significant change?
哪些指标出现了统计学意义上的变化？
First, determine which metrics showed us statistically significant difference,
首先 确定哪个指标展示了统计学意义上的差异
with the individual alpha for each metric at 0.05.
用每个指标单独的 α 值 0.05
Next, set your overall alpha to 0.05 and
接下来 将总的 α 值设置为 0.05
use the Bonferroni correction to calculate the individual alpha.
使用 Bonferroni 校正来计算单个的 α 值
As a reminder,
记住
here's how to calculate the individual alpha using the Bonferroni correction.
怎样用 Bonferroni 校正计算单个 α 值
For each method and each metric,
每一个方法 每一个指标
check the box if that metric showed a statistically significant difference.
如果那个指标显示了统计学意义上的差异 勾选这个方框
Do you think the Bonferroni method is overly conservative here or
你认为 Bonferroni 校正法在这里过于保守吗？
is it appropriate?
还是正合适？